[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "How can you include an external javascript file?",
    "answer": "/script src='myfile.js'/"
  },

  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "How can you determine if something is NaN?",
    "answer": "use isNaN() function."
  },

  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What's the best way to copy array myArr into newArr?",
    "answer": "newArr = myArr.slice( ) or slice( 0 );"
  },

  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "var a = [a,b,c,d,e]. What does b = a.splice() do?",
    "answer": "a will become an empty array and b will become [a,b,c,d,e]"
  },

  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Turn 'Tom', 'Bill', 'Jerry' into the string 'Tom, Bill, Jerry'",
    "answer": "Use array.join(', ')"
  },

  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is a function declaration compared to a function expression?",
    "answer": "declaration: function myFunc(){ ... }, expression: var myFunc = function() { ... }"
  },

  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "How could you get today’s day (e.g. “Monday”) from the date object?",
    "answer": "You need to make an array with Sunday at 0 index and Saturday at 7 index. Then use getDay() and find the day using your array."
  },

  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What does a for ... in loop do and what does it look like?",
    "answer": "It iterates over the enumerable properties in an object like this: for (var prop in obj) {// optionally, find only properties of this object, not the objects from which it inherits if (obj.hasOwnProperty(prop) { // do something"
  },

  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "How do you access the function you are in (e.g. for a factorial)?",
    "answer": "Use the name of the function. Arguments.caller is deprecated."
  },

  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "var s = String; typeof s will be what?",
    "answer": "'function'"
  }
]
